>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们来谈谈 == 具体与 Booleans的情况。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk about
== specifically with Booleans.
这是另一个你不应该做的最邪恶角落的例子。
This is another one of those really
evil corner cases that you shouldn't do.
你在密码里做了很多事情
This is something that
you do a lot in code, and
那肯定是你不该做的
it's something you should
definitely not do.
这是因为你习惯用其他语言来做这件事
It's something you do because you're used
to doing this in other languages, and
这会让你惹上麻烦的
here, it's gonna get you into trouble.
好吧如果你想看看你是否愿意
Okay, if you wanna check
if you want to allow
将数组的布尔值强制为 true。
the Boolean coercion of
an array to be true.
换句话说，你想说它的真实的构造。
In other words, you wanna say
its truthy sort of construct.
那是我可以接受的
That is something that I'm okay with.
有些人一点也不明白
Some people are not okay with that.
但让我们说你是暂时的
But let's say that you do for the moment.
有一种方法，就是做一个 if 语句。
There's one way of doing it,
which is just just to do an if statement.
允许 if 语句在数组上调用布尔运算，
Allow the if statement to invoke the to
Boolean operation on the array, which,
在这种情况下，是一种查找，表示数组不在表上，因此，
in this case, is a lookup that says
the array is not on the table, so,
所以，这是真的。
therefore, it's true.
这是一个完全理性的布尔胁迫的暗示。
That's a perfectly rational
implicit to Boolean coercion.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 但如果你试着变得更聪明，更狡猾，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But if you try to get
more clever and tricky with it and say,
如果它是真实的
well, if it's truthy,
也许我该做的就是做一个真正的双方面的人
then maybe what I ought to do
is do a double equals with true.
好吧现在突然都不起作用了
Well, now all of a sudden it doesn't work.
顺便说下，三等功也不起作用。
And by the way, it wouldn't
work with triple equals either.
将与 Boolean 的比较 Cuz 将通过一系列的
Cuz the comparison with a Boolean to an
array is gonna go through a bunch of those
我们已经辨认出来了我们要重新确认
corner cases, which we've already
identified and we're about to re-identify.
而且这也会是假的
And also it's gonna be equal to false.
所以现在你要把你的直觉告诉我
So now you're gonna get the backwards
of what you would intuitively expect.
你觉得这件事是真实的不是真的
You think this thing is truthy,
it is not double equal to true, but
它是双等于假的。
it is double equal to false.
毫无疑问这是一个 " gotcha" 。
And there's no question
that this is a gotcha.
但在我解释这个问题之前，我的答案是永远不会有双重的结果，
But before I even explain the gotcha, my
answer to this is don't ever do a double,
如果你能避免三重的情况的话
or even in that case,
if you can avoid triple.
但绝对不能双等于真假或双数等于假。
But definitely, never do a double equals
with true or a double equals with false.
因为没有场景你需要用真实的和真实的
Because there's no scenario where you
need to do a double equals with true or
当您只能隐式地执行布尔运算时，双值等于 false 。
double equals with false when you could
just do the to Boolean implicitly.
没必要那样做更好
There's no case where that or
that is better.
还有一堆情况比这个更糟好吗
And there's a bunch of cases where
it's worse, like this one, okay?
因此，让我们解释 == true 如何失败，但 == false 是有效的。
So let's explain how the == true fails but
the == false works.
相同步骤，相同算法。
Same steps, same algorithm.
我们从最上面的一个开始
We start with the top one.
当然，如果是作坊学生，我们只是在这方面做一个布尔值。
Of course if workshop students,
we just do a to Boolean on it.
第四行我们检查它的布尔值
Line 4, we check for
the Boolean on it, and
如果它很匹配，那么在这种情况下，我们就会运行这个核心分支。
if it matches great, in this case it does,
so we run that core branch.
但当我们试图把它等同于真实的时候会发生什么呢 ?
But what happens when we're trying
to double equal it with true?
我们有一个很原始的非原始的
Well, we have a non-primitive
which need to became primitive, so
它会变成空字符串。
it becomes empty string.
我们有一个空的字符串和一个真实的
We have an empty string and a true.
这些类型不是相同的类型，因此它们都需要成为数字。
These are not the same type, so
they need to both become numbers.
其中一个变为 0，应该是 NaN，另一个变为 1。
One of them becomes 0, which should
have been NaN, the other one becomes 1.
这两个数字肯定不相等，所以我们不运行那个代码分支。
And those two numbers are definitely not
equal, so we don't run that code branch.
在另一个代码分支中，我们做了同样的事情。
In the other code branch
we do the exact same thing.
我们从作坊开始，学生是假的。
We start off with workshop
students = false.
我们到达一个字符串 = false，该字符串将变为 0 ，而与 0 相比，
We get to a string = false,
which becomes a 0 compared to a 0, and
这些都是真实的
those 0s are equal to true.
这是一个非耸耸听的结果。这是一个非耸耸听的构造。
That's a nonsensical outcome to
what was a nonsensical construct.
你不需要双重等于是真的
You don't need to double equals to true,
or
double 等于 false，允许隐式发生布尔值。
double equals to false,
allow the to Boolean to happen implicitly.
但又一次
So yet again,
我想说的是暗示有时比显的好得多
what I'm saying is that implicit is
sometimes much better than explicit.
在此情况下，隐式不包含 gotcha 和 explicit 。
In this case, the implicit doesn't
have the gotcha and the explicit does.
>> 演讲者 1: 这可能是一个过于宽泛的问题，太笼统，但在其他情况下
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: This is maybe too broad a
question, too generic, but in other cases
在那里你会更进一步，而不是在作坊学生的时候跑出来。
where you would go a step further and
rather than running if workshop students.
你会检查所有车间学生的情况
You would check if and
then method all workshop students,
检查是否存在 .length 以确保其为字符串或
checking the presence of .length
to make sure it's a string or
或者您正在检查其他类型的特定类型。
an array, or
you're checking other type specific.
>> Kyle Simpson: 因此，此构造的方案是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
the scenario of this construct is
我只想知道不管有没有设定
I only wanna know whether it's set or not.
我知道它可以被解开
And I know that it can either be unset or
它可以被设置成一个数组，就是这个场景的心理构造。
it can be set to an array, that was
the mental construct of this scenario.
那么周围的代码的其余部分都是显而易见的
So that would have been obvious by
the rest of the surrounding code or
至少有希望能从周围的代码中清楚显示
at least hopefully obvious from
the rest of the surrounding code.
如果我们不知道，如果我们知道它可能是未设的，或者它可以被设定和
If we didn't know that, if we knew that
it could be unset, or it could be set and
它可以被设置成各种不同的事物，也许是一个数组，也许是一个物体，
it could be set to a variety of different
things, maybe an array, maybe an object,
也许是绳子
maybe a string.
那我们就想做些更深入的调查
Then we would wanna do some sort of
deeper checking than just the to Boolean
强迫。
coercion.
这可能是检验实际设置的第一步，
That might be the first step to
check that it is actually set, and
接下来的检查就是检查它的身份
then the next check is to check
something about its identity.
你可以用各种方法来检查它。
And there's various ways
that you could check it.
如果合适，您可以使用类型的运算符。
You could use a type of operator,
if that was appropriate.
你可以做你所说的
You could do what you're referring to,
这叫做鸭式打字，看看是否有办法，
which is called duck typing,
check to see if a method is on it,
您可以执行类似 array.isarray 的实际实用程序来检查它是否处于数组中。
you could do an actual utility like
array.isarray to check if it's in array.
有很多其他的事情你想做的话
There's a variety of other things
that you might wanna do if you
特别了解它是一个阵列。
cared to specifically
know it was an array.
但我在这里的设置是我们已经知道这是一个阵列
But the setup I have here is that we
would already know it's an array,
我们已经看到第一线了
cuz we already see line 1.
可以设置，也可以是数组，
It can either be set or
it can be an array,
这两者之间就没什么关系了
and it can't be anything else in between.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
>> 演讲者 1: 是的，我想我的问题是，如果你愿意
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, and I guess my
question is if you would typically advise
就像鸭子打字进第 3 行吗
against packing it like duck typing
into line 3 into that check?
正在尝试合并两者。
Trying to combine both.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 不，这不是我要说的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: No,
that's not what I'm saying.
我想说的是如果出于某种原因我不能限制
What I'm saying is I would do those if for
some reason I couldn't restrict
我想知道这不是一个集合或是一个数组
myself to know that it's
either an unset or an array.
我宁愿选择较细小的面积，而无须进行所需的检查。
I would prefer a smaller surface
area with fewer necessary checks.
我更喜欢设计这个代码，让它不会那么多态。
I would prefer to design this code so
that it's not so polymorphic.
要么完全取消要么是一个数组
It's either unset entirely or
it's an array.
但如果出于某种原因我不能用那种方式来设计我的代码
But if for some reason I couldn't
design my code in that way,
那我就把这些额外的支票放进去
then I would put those extra
checks into the if statement.
有什么帮助吗
Does that help?
>> 扬声器 1: 是的，这很棒。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Yeah, that's great.
>> 凯尔辛普森: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.